I just patched it for the first time.
初 め にパッチしてはじめです
When you choose the second one, check out Pink Bath's pecks and review.
2つ目を選んだときは、ピンクのバースのペッキスとレビューを
Hair candy in front of my hand, Peri's.
手の前に髪飴、ペリの、
A classic textured face.
定 番のキメ顔
3、2、1
Please let me take the picture again.
もう一度撮影させてください
A classic sharp face.
定番のキメ顔
It came out like this.
こんな感じに出たよ
Get ready, Lee.
準備、リー
Do you want to prepare?
準備してみ?
Ride your face and pouch beautifully and give it the best swing.
顔もポーチも綺麗に乗って、最高の振りに仕上げて
Be careful of the curtain behind you and stand with your toes on the standing position line.
後ろのカーテンに気をつけて、立ち位置ラインにつま先を足して立
Ride beautifully.
て て、 綺麗に乗って
I'm sure it will turn out well.
きっとから、よく仕上がりな
start!
スタート!
How about something like this?
こんな風にどうだろう?
2、1
Get along well and be alone.
仲良く、一人
Isn't this moving?
これって動いてるじゃない?
If you don't look at the camera, it won't leak, 1.
カメラを見ないと漏れないから、 1、
Can ride for 2, 3, 4, 5 seconds
2、3、4、5秒間乗り出せる
Yo.
よ
Open Meijers.
マ イジャーズ開けて
While having one Meijers.
マイジャーズを1個しながら
Black sucks.
ブラックへつらせる
Black flatters me.
ブラックへつらして
Open it with one Meijer.
マイジャーズを1個しながら開ける
Show your butt a little too.
お尻もちょっとつけ出して
Even if your head knows it, your heart can't keep up with your body. It's simple.
頭じゃ分かっていても 心が追いつかない体は シンプルハロネ
Even more so because you're a man. Even if you waver and sway, you're still the one.
男 だから なおさらね よらよらゆらゆらいても 未だに君が一
It was the worst and I loved it.I don't know why, but I've forgotten.
番 最低で 大好きだった なんでかな ムカつくわ もう忘れ
I want to
ちゃ いたい
When I went to the donation room at 8 o'clock, it was a mess, and I was alone again.
の 寄付室にかけた8時 散らかった 一人また身体 許してしま
It seems like I'll be okay even if you're gone, so don't throw me away
った あなたがいなくなっても あたしは平気そうで 捨てないで
Let me be mean
意 地悪くなさせてよ
In front of me, with an innocent face
あ たしの前で 無 邪気な顔で
...
Shut the door shut and the two of you can't do anything about it. It's disgusting.
静 かに閉めて どうにもならない二人だ 気 持ち悪い ドログ
I'll do it, sweetheart, it's okay to stay here, I want you to smile just for now.
に するから 恋人ここでいいから 今だけ笑っていてほしい 病
I'm tired of walking up the slope with all my baggage, but what I can forget is
気 の荷物に 歩き疲れた坂道だ 忘れていいのは
What you can hide and forget forever
隠 しさで ずっと 忘れていいのは
Welcome, welcome
い らっしゃい いらっしゃい
stamp stamp
ス タンプ スタンプ
I'll leave
離 れますよ
Are you going to leave the stamps?
ス タンプ離れちゃうか
I wonder if you're going to take off your shoes now.
今 チンだろうか 靴脱いで 下
from open
から 開いて
Run, run, run
走 って走って
Thank you for watching.
ご 視聴ありがとうございました
And thank you for watching.
そして、ご視聴ありがとうございました